

# Theodor Anderberg Törngren

I am a fifth-year student of Engineering Physics at LTH with a specialization in Machine Learning. I have several experiences of working with software development in both industrial and academic settings and a passion for solving difficult problems together and understanding new concepts.

### **Experience**

## Ericsson, Lund — Summer Internship R&D

June 2024 - August 2024

This summer I returned to the Beam Forming Control team and continued the development of internal tools. I mostly worked with an existing internal tool written in **Python** consisting of **several tens of thousands of lines of code**. This immensely improved my ability to work with large and complex codebases.

#### **Ericsson**, Lund — Summer Internship R&D

June 2023 - August 2023

I worked as an intern in the **Agile Scrum** team for the Beam Forming Control team at Ericsson. During my internship, I developed multiple internal tools and websites with **Python** and **JavaScript React**.

#### **Lund University**, Lund — *Teaching Assistant in 3 programming courses*

January 2022 – December 2023

I have been a Teaching Assistant in the courses: Programming: First Course, Programming: Second Course, and Concurrent Programming for a **total of 8 separate course offerings**. As a Teaching Assistant, I have helped students and given feedback on their programming projects in **Java** and **C**. The three courses have **23 unique projects** of varying complexity.

#### **Lund University**, Lund — SI-Leader and Coach

August 2021 - December 2022

As an SI-Leader I held cooperative learning classes in Calculus for Computer Science students. As an SI-Coach I gave feedback to several SI-Leaders, helping them improve their cooperative learning classes.

#### **Education**

## **Lund University**, Lund — Master of Science: Engineering Physics

August 2020 - Present GPA: 4.63/5.00

#### **The University of Edinburgh**, Edinburgh — Exchange: School of Informatics

January 2024 - May 2024

GPA: 79.5/100 (Excellent, 1st Honours Classification)

#### **Johannes Hedberggymnasiet**, Helsingborg — Natural Science Programme

August 2017 - June 2020

GPA: 22.5/22.5

Kakelvägen 6A Lund, 22730 Sweden (+46) 72 329 50 75 theodor.anderberg. torngren@gmail.com

#### Skills

- Problem-solving
- Machine Learning
- Programming
- Mathematics
- Physics

## Extracurricular activities

**Daytime Staff** at Skane Climbing Club 2022-2023

**Lounge Host** at Arkad Career Fair 2022

**Mentor** for new students at Lund University 2022

**Tutor** for new students at Lund University 2022

**Mentor** for new students at Lund University 2021

Kitchen Worker at the Engineering Physics Council of Festivities

### Languages

**Swedish** - Native Language

English - C2 Level

Spanish - B1 Level

#### **Certificates**

Cambridge Advanced English Grade: A, CEFR Level: C2

Drivers Licence Am & B